{
    "subject": "resource/Galway_County_Council_election,_2004",
    "predicate": "ontology/startDate",
    "object": "2004-06-11",
    "human_readable": "The start date of Galway County Council election, 2004 is June 11, 2004.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9865476489067078,
            "question": "What was the starting date of the Galway County Council election in 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9861635565757751,
            "question": "On what date did the Galway County Council election begin in 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.985469400882721,
            "question": "What is the start date of the Galway County Council election from 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9854577779769897,
            "question": "If the Galway County Council election began on June 11th, 2004, what is the month and day?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.968726396560669,
            "question": "What was the date of the commencement of the Galway County Council election in 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9684969186782837,
            "question": "When did the Galway County Council election take place in 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9399755597114563,
            "question": "What significant political event occurred on June 11th, 2004 in Galway County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8999090194702148,
            "question": "Which event commenced on June 11th, 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8623957633972168,
            "question": "June 11th, 2004, marks the beginning of which event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8521085977554321,
            "question": "In what year did the Galway County Council election start on June 11th?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The start date of Galway County Council election, 2004 is June 11, 2004.",
            "html": "dbpedia_343_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=June 11th, 2004, marks the beginning of which event?",
            "html": "dbpedia_343_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which event commenced on June 11th, 2004?",
            "html": "dbpedia_343_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant political event occurred on June 11th, 2004 in Galway County?",
            "html": "dbpedia_343_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_343_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents state that \"An election to Galway County Council took place on 11 June 2004 as part of that year's Irish local elections,\" which supports the query about the start date of the Galway County Council election in 2004."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}